<resources>
	<string name = "app_name">Seguime</string>

	<string name = "traducidopor">Javier Martínez (usando traductor)</string>


	<string name = "menu_abrir">Menu</string>
	<string name = "menu_cerrar">Close Menu</string>

	<string name = "bloquear">Block</string>
	<string name = "unlock">Unlock</string>

	<string name = "servidor">Server</string>
	<string name = "usuario">User</string>
	<string name = "clave">Key</string>
	<string name = "intervalo_inactividad">Idle interval (in seconds)</string>
	<string name = "intervalo_actividad">Activity Interval (in seconds)</string>
	<string name = "intervalo_internet">Interval between internet connections</string>
	<string name = "sms">SMS</string>
	<string name = "id_telegram">Chat_ID Telegram (17###...)</string>
	<string name = "rastreo">Tracking (Sends Messages)</string>
	<string name = "telegram_bot">Telegram Bot</string>
	<string name = "iniciarConElSistema">Start with system</string>
	<string name = "activarconpantalla">Start activity when turning on the screen(User log in)</string>
	<string name = "enviarInfo">Send connection information</string>
	<string name = "conectarseRedesAbiertas">Connect to open networks (Requires Wifi Automágico app)</string>
	<string name = "permitirConfigurarSMS">Allow SMS to be configured from server</string>
	<string name = "permitirActivar">Allow to activate the application from the server (Requires internet connection interval)</string>
	<string name="permitirActivarSMS">Activate tracking mode when receive SMS: Seguime</string>

	<string name = "opcionesDeRastreo">The following options will be enabled when trace mode is active</string>
	<string name = "enviarFotografias">Send Photos (Requires Cámara Espía App)</string>

	<string name="zona_horaria_servidor">Server time zone</string>

	<string name = "errorValidacion">There is an error with the data entered</string>

	<string name = "espere">Please wait... </string>

	<string name = "permitir_activar_boton_panico">Allow activation </string>

	<string name = "boton_de_panico">Panic button</string>



	<string name = "sesion_clavedesigual">Keys DO NOT match</string>
	<string name = "sesion_clavecorta">The keys are very short</string>
	<string name = "sesion_usuariocorto">The username is very short</string>
	<string name = "sesion_sinservidor">You must specify a server</string>

	<string name = "cerrarsesion_mensajeadvertencia">This will delete all data. Are you sure? </string>


	<string name = "latitud">Latitude</string>
	<string name = "longitud">Longitude</string>
	<string name = "fechahora">Date and Time</string>
	<string name = "fecha">Date</string>
	<string name = "hora">Time</string>
	<string name = "infoextra">Extra information</string>

	<string name = "contactos">Contacts</string>

	<string name = "configuracion">Configuration</string>
	<string name = "opciones">Options</string>
	<string name = "guardar">Save</string>
	<string name = "cancelar">Cancel</string>
	<string name = "editar">Edit</string>
	<string name = "registros">Logs</string>
	<string name = "cerrar_sesion">Logout</string>
	<string name = "salir">Exit</string>

	<string name = "velocidad">Speed</string>

	<string name = "registros_coordenadas">Coordinate Records</string>
	<string name = "registros_imagenes">Image Logs</string>



	<string name = "txt_bloqueado_alarma">Service cannot be stopped when an alarm is activated</string>
	<string name = "alarma">Alarm (Alert Message)</string>
	<string name = "alarmamensaje">At this time you may need help, contact me urgently</string>
	<string name = "iniciar">Start</string>
	<string name = "detener">Stop</string>
	<string name = "mensajealerta">Alert Message</string>

	<string name = "minuto">Minute</string>
	<string name = "segundo">Second</string>

	<string name = "principal_alarma">The alarm activated</string>
	<string name = "principal_rastreo">Tracker is On</string>
	<string name = "principal_aplicacion">The application is enabled</string>
	<string name = "principal_internet">There is an internet connection</string>
	<string name = "principal_alarmaservidor">There is a copy of the alarm on the server</string>




	<string name = "txt_servicio_activo">Okay! The application is Enabled :-)</string>
	<string name = "txt_servicio_inactivo">The application is disabled, press the button to activate it</string>
	<string name = "txt_bloqueado">At this point the application is blocked</string>

	<string name = "activar_aplicacion">¡Seguime!</string>
	<string name = "desactivar_aplicacion">Seguime</string>

	<string name = "cuentaregresiva">Countdown</string>

	<string name = "ayuda">Help</string>
	<string name = "cerrar">Close</string>






	<string name = "iniciarsesion">Login</string>
	<string name = "registrarse">Register</string>
	<string name = "repetirclave">Repeat key (DO NOT USE real keys)</string>
	<string name = "ssl">SSL secure connection</string>

	<string name = "registrarAplicacion">Register Version</string>
	<string name = "nombre">Name</string>
	<string name = "versionRegistrada">Registered Version</string>
	<string name = "claveIncorrecta">Incorrect key</string>
	<string name = "requiereregistro">Requires FREE registration, visit the website</string>
	<string name = "txt_registrodeversion">Registration is FREE, visit the website and get your key, does not require personal information</string>

	<string name = "requiresforgivenacion">This is an incomplete version, visit website</string>



	<string name = "conectando">Connecting... </string>
	<string name = "errorconexion">Connection error</string>
	<string name = "enviando">Sending data.... </string>
	<string name = "recibiendo">Receiving data... </string>
	<string name = "conexionfinalizada">Connection complete. </string>




	<string name = "presentacion_dispositivo">Find your device</string>
	<string name = "presentacion_servidor">Use your own Server</string>
	<string name = "presentacion_alerta">Send alert messages</string>
	<string name = "presentacion_remoto">Set up the application remotely</string>



	<string name = "txt_ayuda_descripcion">
	Seguime allows you to track your device,
	collects GPS information and stores it for later sending to your server.
	From the server you can view the logs on a map and see where the device is (or was).
	The server can be that of a friend, family member or yours,
	you can mount your own server for greater privacy of your data.
	It also includes a timer that allows you to program when the app will activate its tracking mode
	and additionally send a message of help.
	When the app is in tracking mode it will send sms or Telegram messages with the location.
	</string>

	<string name = "txt_advertencia_proyecto">
	This is a project, it is not (or is not intended to be) a security application,
	it is for experimental use only.
	The developer (or developers and contributors)
	are not and will not be liable for the use or misuse of these programs
	(applications, website, source codes, etc.).
	</string>



	<string name = "txt_licencia">
	This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
	it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
	the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
	(at your option) any later version. \n

	This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
	but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the warranty implied
	MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the
	GNU General Public License for more details. \n

	You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
	along with this program. If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/
	</string>






	<string name = "dona">Make a Donation :)</string>
	<string name = "sitioweb">Go to website</string>
	<string name="ir_al_canal_telegram">Go to Telegram Channel</string>
	<string name = "txt_donacion">
	If you like the App you can collaborate with a donation.
	Please note that this Application has no advertising, sponsor, or trackers, therefore it depends solely on the collaboration of users.
	</string>

	<string name = "txt_colaboracion_desarrolladores">
	Do you like free apps?. \n
	You can collaborate by making donations to developers so they can continue programming your favorite apps. \n
	</string>

	<string name = "txt_ayuda_opciones">
	You will see that it is not that complicated, you have the following options:
	\n

	SMS:
	It is a phone number that you can choose for the application to send coordinates by SMS. \n
	SMS will only be sent if tracking is enabled. \n
	To avoid expenses I recommend you DO NOT USE THIS OPTION if you are using the Tracking server, use this option ONLY if you are using your own server, or a secure server
	\n
	Telegram ID:
	It is a Telegram identifier number, NOT THE @ID_USUARIO, to use this option visit the bot @seguimebot and say hello, it will give you your ID number, then with that number the bot will be able to send coordinates to that Telegram account. \n
	\n
	Activity Interval:
	During this period the Application will be fully functioning, locating coordinates and making internet connections, a very small value may not be able to obtain coordinates if you have little GPS coverage, a very high value can consume a lot of battery
	In order for the application to be constantly on (and not by time intervals) set any time interval to 0 (zero)
	\n
	Idle Interval:
	During this period the Application will be resting, will not make internet connections or locate coordinates, a rest serves to save battery, a very small value may consume a lot of battery, a very high value will hinder the purpose of the app
	In order for the application to be constantly on (and not by time intervals) set any time interval to 0 (zero)
	\n
	Tracking:
	When this option is enabled the application will send messages by Telegram and SMS each time it finds a new coordinate. This option can be enabled from the website therefore for your security and to avoid expenses do not configure SMS unless you are using your own server
	\n
	\n
	I hope you find this help useful :)
	\n
	\n
	\n
	</string>




	<string name = "txt_ayuda_regresiva">
	Timer Help:
	\n
	It allows you to schedule a countdown, once activated it will do the following:
	1. Set the phone number to send text messages. \n
	2. Leave the app in activated mode, the application can only be disabled if no timers are programmed. \n
	3. Send a copy of the countdown to the server. \n
	\n
	At the end of the countdown, you will trigger an alarm that will do the following:
	1. It will put the application into tracking mode. \n
	2. Send a programmed SMS with the chosen text. \n
	3. The server will send messages via Telegram.  \n
	\n
	</string>



	<string name = "txt_firma">
	Made in Argentina by Javier Martínez
	</string>

	<string name = "versionIncompleta_txt">Some options are not available on this version</string>


</resources>
